The reason I'm at this cockeyed angle is that we are at the spot on the Needles Highway,
just maybe a mile in, where it goes to a one lane stone tunnel.
And a charter bus is trying to get through here.
And I just had to get video of this.
Because I can't imagine this thing is going to make it through here.
And even if he gets through, this route is so windy that, and I was commenting on the
way up here, that I can't imagine a charter bus coming through here because it's too long
to go around these hairpin turns.
Or near hairpin.
But he's obviously making it, but I wouldn't want to try it.
So he's waving at some people, apparently they're...
Boy, that's an up close and personal look at the...
And the people are cheering because he made it through there.
I can't believe he made it.
And if someone would have told me, I would have told them they were full of it.