Hey Miffy, do you know what this is?
Do you want some cat food?
No?
What else do we have?
We got some other kind of food.
We got some dog food.
Can cats eat dog food?
Do you think she'll eat dog food?
You say, what do you say?
Yes or no?
Yes!
Yes.
You think she'll eat dog food?
Yes?
Alright.
Look at this Miff.
You want to eat this dog food?
Huh?
What is this?
Does it look good to you?
I don't believe it.
She's eating it.
Hey you eat that dog food.
That's good stuff.
You want to eat this?
No.
No?
You can't eat it.
Ah, it's moving around too much on her so I'm going to get a plate for her.
I just need to try and see if their cat loves it because I don't believe that Miffy actually
loves it.
We should put on the label pet food for dog and cat.
For dogs and cats.
Miffy really likes that stuff.
Mmm mmm.
She ate that big part.
Oh yeah, that's good.
Just to let you guys know that are watching this, our cat is really picky.
There's a lot of cat food that she won't eat.
This is kind of strange to see her eating dog food.
But she really likes this dog food so I might have to buy this again.
If she doesn't get sick off of it, I'll buy it again.
It's a, oh, Miffy.
Alright, it's good stuff.
I like it when she shakes her head, it's fun.
Feels good.
It's the Miffy Show.
Now she's looking at me.
Miff, Miff, Miff it up.
Hey, this is Miffy's show.
We just fed our cat dog food.
That's kind of funny.
Yeah, she really liked it.
She did.
I knew it.
That was fun, wasn't it?
Yeah, that was fun.
Yeah, I was talking to her though, it was fun to eat the dog food.
It was fun for us too.
Yeah, it sure is.
I don't believe a cat can eat dog food.
Busted.
Bust, busted.
Well, Miffy survived the night.
She ate dog food and didn't get sick, did you Miff?
You're pretty healthy, you feel good?
Taking some good naps today?
You didn't get sick, did you?
Huh?
You all right?
Still got your fat belly?
You can see that she really liked her dog food.
She ate most of it, made a little bit of a mess.
But that's pretty good.
She ate more of the dog food than she eats of a lot of cat food brands.
So yes, cats can eat dog food.
Yay!