Here we are at Saigon Sandwich.
So this is the tofu sandwich.
It's very nice.
Let me just move it around a bit.
Very nice.
Great.
Asian Art Museum.
Eating the sandwich.
How is it?
Really good.
Really good eh?
Yeah.
You are really really close.
This is the mixed combination.
Go away birds.
Birds too close.
It's special.
Oh that's what I do.
So what kind of dessert is this?
It's a Vietnamese bean pudding.
Bean pudding?
It's called Jea.
Nice.
How is it?
Really good.
Really good?
Authentic eh?
Yep.
So apparently there is rice inside.
Oh yeah.
What is this?
Very interesting.
What is it made out of?
There is rice and it's wrapped inside a banana leaf, stuffed pork and steamed.
Wow.
It's really good.
You can see the inside there.
How is it?
Good.
It's like a version of the evil castle.