Buenos Aires is a city for the fashion conscious.
Everybody wants to look good.
But dressing up isn't just for porteños.
Being out on the town presentable is just as important for the dogs.
But if you are a dog, where do you go for your beauty treatments?
At Sebastians in Recoleta, dogs big and small come in for a model makeover.
There are hundreds of dog beauty parlors in the city.
Here at Sebastians, the man to see is Hugo.
There is no service that he won't do.
Hugo grooms and styles around 25 dogs a day.
But some customers need more convincing than others.
Down here, everyone knows who the boss is.
But when he comes here, he calms down and stays in Hugo's hands.
He is the only one who knows how to groom and cut.
Sprucing up isn't always the most pleasant experience.
But when you look good, you feel good.
There are dogs that come to the door, go and jump on the doorstep, alone.
They come to a comfortable place, where they can meet other animals.
They live happily here.
Bye, Cecilia.
Bye, Hugo.