Bike Friendly Cities is a European project that wants to get cities cycling.
Southend-on-Sea in Cambridge in the UK, Middelburg and the province of Zeeland in the Netherlands,
Boulogne in France and Kortrijk in Belgium are all working together to promote cycling
in their cities.
In summer 2013, these cities held bike parades and invited everyone to come along, dress
up and celebrate cycling.
My name's Steve and this is Chris and we're on Southend Cycle Ride.
We like cycling because it's out in the fresh air, you make lots of new friends and have
a really good time.
It's good for the environment as well.
It's nice to get out on the bike and meet other people.
Do you cycle to work?
Yes, daily.
Daily?
Every day you go to work on your bicycles?
Yes.
Hi, I'm Kritika.
I love cycling because it's fun, it keeps me fit, it's cheap and it keeps my carbon
footprint down.
I'm Fran and I like cycling because it's cheap, I get there fast and I get a cheap
ride.
I really have a race bicycle.
Some do it on the professional side, others do it for leisure.
For me it's also a matter of moving and taking out the stress.
The whole week is a lot of stress.
When the weather is a bit fine, like today, I can do some cycling.
I live in Kortrijk in Belgium.
The bike is the best way to find our way in the city.
It inspires me as well.
Bye.