There's a slogan that reads,
charging an electric car is charging the energy
of the earth.
This means that you get to play a role
in reducing greenhouse gas emissions
by driving eco-friendly vehicles.
An exhibition took place to showcase a wide range
of electric cars and related equipment.
Let's take a look.
This is an electric car that emits less carbon dioxide
and air pollutants.
If you connect this car with a charger,
it provides electric current through a transmission.
The Ministry of Environment, Seoul Metropolitan Government
and Korea Environment Corporation have jointly
established infrastructure for electric cars.
Last year, we established a charging system to feed
up to 500 electric cars.
We plan to build another one with a capacity
of 2,600 vehicles this year.
And if this takes place, more electric cars will come
into place, which will lead to carbon emissions reduction
and air quality improvement.
This is a machine that accesses data of electric voltage
and current for efficient use of electric vehicles.
As it can estimate the efficiency rate,
it's useful when conducting research and development.
The 2012 electric vehicle
and smart car exhibition was held on October 17th
to display eco-friendly electric vehicles
and related equipment.
Manufacturers of electric vehicles,
related industries including two-wheeled vehicles,
parts and materials,
charging systems participated in this exhibition.
This is a business fair that is aimed
at facilitating exchanges between professionals
in the electric vehicle industry.
This fair presented diverse electric vehicles,
auto parts and analysis system as well
as all electric battery-powered buses.
Overseas market seminars were held on the sideline
of the event to give information
to Korean electric car manufacturers.
Electric vehicles have reduced greenhouse gas emissions
and air pollutants.
To raise penetration rate of electric cars,
companies will have to endeavor
to develop advanced technologies.