I like really hit the gym, like really thorough that night.
We call ourselves Charlotte Parkour.
We're basically, we are the, we started training parkour about, the first of us started about
70 years ago here at UNC Charlotte and since then we've grown into a bigger group.
Other people have started to join us, we've progressed, a lot of us have learned, met
other people.
Parkour is a discipline of training your mind and body to overcome obstacles.
We train this by running, jumping, climbing, vaulting, balancing, things like that.
If you want to try a new jump, you're not just, you don't just physically jump, at the
same time you have to overcome the mental fear and like the, overcoming the obstacle
process.
So, it's a process of breaking down obstacles like in your head and figuring out the different
parts and training those parts, bringing it back together and then it's also a process
of facing the fear.
So, you might be physically capable of doing a new jump or some new move, but at the same
time there's a fear like telling you like, oh you're going to get hurt and you have to
suppress that fear, like learn to control it and at the same time listen to it, you
know, know when it's right and when you know better.
We teach now, we teach classes here, we teach seminars, hoping to share what we know with
other people.
Really, everyone's kind of been standing around, I just want everyone really to kind of do
like this on each leg, this is going to just kind of get our ankles warmed up a little
bit.
While we're doing this, let's go ahead and warm up our wrists some.
So, just kind of roll your wrists like this.
Rolls are something that can save your life or your knee.
I tore two muscles in my knee because I fell off a building and I didn't roll.
My leg buckled to the side, but had I actually rolled, I would have been okay.
Core decision, so this is something that will definitely come in handy and if you've ever
seen people do the dive rolls, that's what I'm going to be teaching you too.
So we'll start with rolls on the ground, fall rolls and then dive rolls.
Push off and really drive your shoulder, everything into the ground.
The way that I learned best to do this is that you swing with your foot through, that'll
provide your body with the motion up you need and your hands are just there to support you
when you come back down.
So it's a little bit weird, but basically watch how I'm using my right foot on the jump,
that'll pick me up, my hands are only there to support me on the way back down.
So coming through, I'll just go here.
How many people have you tried before?
Smile about it.
You ready to let go?
Yeah!
Scoot on over.
Is that for me?
Please do.
There was some episode of Avatar, this guy's teasing a prison guard.
Okay, who's pinching who's nipple?
Whom?