I totally jacked up his bum.
Good morning, happy Saturday.
I do not look my best right now.
I think I feel a little bit better.
Or I'm just on so many drugs that it doesn't hurt.
And I'm gonna give Bentley a bath and a trim
because I don't like the way that he came out
when I took him to the groomer.
Last week I feel like she just scissored him
and I don't like it.
So I'm gonna do this ish myself.
So I'm gonna give him a bath, blow him out.
I ordered the Wahl Brevara Clipper Set
and that should be delivered any minute now by FedEx.
So I figure I would just wash and blow him out
even though he's already kind of clean.
But everything I read about using clippers and clipping dogs
the clippers just work best when they are clean.
Not they're clean, when the dog's clean.
So I figure I'll just get this part out of the way.
Not gonna use a white shampoo
because I believe they used one on him at the groomers.
I'm gonna use this Earth Bath Puppy Shampoo
for blueberry facial for his face.
And I'm gonna use the Thick and Thicker
and the After You Base
because I enjoy the results that I get with that.
I think I'm just gonna, unless I completely fail at this mission
I'm just gonna groom him myself because
clippers were expensive.
And I'm just wearing the apron because it makes me feel like
you know, legit.
People that wear aprons, they know what they're doing.
Ready, Bubbles?
I'm gonna fill up the sink.
Fill it up, fill it up.
Whoops, look at my fluffy fluff flufferson.
He has like a little fro.
And he's all clean and dry.
I'm actually quite pleased with my work.
Uh-uh, hunty, uh-uh.
And I think I kinda desensitized him to the hair dryer
in his face
because I just rapid-fired kibble at him
when I was using the blow dryer and the parts that he didn't like
because I read in a dog training book
how to desensitize him and I think it worked a little bit.
I was able to actually blow out his head
and it's not all wavy.
I mean, I could've blew him out better but you know what?
I think I actually did a pretty good job.
Even though your face is a little dirty.
So now I'm just gonna let him play
and we're waiting for our clippers to be delivered.
You're not gonna go to the groomer no more,
your mama's gonna do it.
Say, my mama's gonna keep me looking fly, yeah.
We are like in the catacombs of Atlantic Station.
And we're gonna get so lost.
Because this parking garage is like so big
and we already messed it up like once.
Rich people parking.
This elevator smells like pee.
There's the concierge.
Oh, she said the concierge.
Let's just hurry.
Yeah.
We're two minutes late
but we're gonna try because we don't give up.
And if it doesn't work, let's just go shopping.
Heck yeah.
Because, well, we're already here.
Ooh, I want some of that good good.
Some of that crawfish bake.
I feel like this is a place you go when you have your life together.
I know, I feel the same.
You have like a family, you understand how parking works.
You have like an actual credit card or not.
Ooh, the exhibition center.
I think we have to take the escalator.
I remember she said something about another escalator.
I couldn't work here because I wouldn't be able to help people get anywhere.
Magic.
What's happening, my boy?
Did you get a haircut?
We need to fix that.
And they came.
I totally jacked up his bum.
Bum hole.
But I'm just gonna leave it.
I'm not gonna try to fix it because then it'll just look stupid.
But that's okay because then it's easier to clean when there's less hair back there.
Do you like your haircut?
So I just need to go back in here and just scissor a little bit.
And he'll be done.
It's not perfect.
When you do something the first time, it's never perfect.
Look at all that hair.
He's getting really wiggly and I'm not feeling good.
I think it's time for me to take some more drugs.
So we're gonna take a little break and we will resume.
It's really not that bad.
Probably needs a little more here.
Say, I look good, mama.
You did a good job.
Oh my god, I like totally jacked up his butt hole.
Do you like it, Barbies?
Do you like your haircut?
So we are done.
This is the pile of hair.
And I'm just gonna, I don't even know what I did.
I just kinda went along with Malti's obsession with what she did in her video.
He has a couple spots that aren't perfect.
But it's my first time.
It's okay.
And also, he just got blown out.
So when his hair grows back and his natural oils come back, it'll blend a lot better.
You look so cute.
You're my little puppy forever and ever.
I do wanna do, I want his legs a little smaller.
And I kinda don't make fun of me, like his butt.
I did way too much.
Show them your butt.
I did too much on your butt.
I'm sorry, my Barbies.
I'm sorry.
I'm gonna call it a night.
I need to get my life back.
I have stuff everywhere.
I love this.
I am never taking him to the groomer again.
Unless I just need his lines touched up.
What I did, I kinda followed the shape he had.
And just kinda clipped out.
She didn't cut him short enough last time.
I like him like that.
And I want his head to grow out.
And I don't know.
I have a plan, but I'm just too tired to talk about it.
So I'm gonna say bye.
Barbies, say goodnight to all your friends.
Bye guys.
She was crazy.
I got a bath, a blow dry, and a haircut.
And a top sprout.
She has a knot, but I don't have a full knot yet.
Cause I'm still a baby puppy.
Can you give him the kisses, my Barbies?
Oh, you're such a sweet Barbie.