आपको इसे बाता है हैं अगर आप पर बाता हैं?
आपको आपको पर बाता हैं!
आपको पर बाता हैं!
Hey people, so have you ever wondered
आप अगर अपने डॉक की कुछ बिमारी
या फिर किसी तकलीफ को
चेक अप करवाएं जाएंगे तो कहां जायेंगे?
So you know, anyone can call us for emergency services.
Call, call, eh... which number?
Emergency number is there, isn't it?
Emergency number?
It's 9810162807
Ma'am any tips you would like to give to
your viewers for their
docking and such. Just keep your pet clean
and healthy and be
very friendly with them. Treat them as your
kid and just
hang out well!
Thank you, ma'am. Thank you very much, ma'am.
So hang out well as ma'am said.
Thank you.
Hey people!
So look at
this awesomeness!
German
Shepherd Dogs!
Competing with each other!
This is the best one.
This is our personal favourite.
And here they are going.
Come on, come on.
What do you think about it?
This is a personality test, okay?
The way they walk,
the way they bark,
and everything is being checked.
Exactly.
Here, especially from Australia,
a judge has come
who is
judging the dogs according to
their agility, their personality,
their moves and all the stuff.
Guys, listen to that.
This one, she's the lady.
She's the lady.
Dori Wander Prestige Trophy.
Look, he's walking nice,
he's walking nice.
How do you think about it, Arpit?
Have you ever watched it before?
No, I really have never.
I never got a chance to go to a dog show.
And guys, there's a show going on there too.
We'll check that out too.
Yes, thank you.
Thanks to Ronaldo for taking me.
I know.
You're too good, man.
Now we'll take you to a mixed dog breed show.
And that's going on there.
Let's check it out.
We're at San Montmere School right now.
So let's go.
This is Labrador Retriever.
Okay, this is Labrador.
And you can check out
here.
Come on, guys.
We'll show you
here.
Check out chicks too.
Wrong thing.
It's my forest to be wrong.
Wait, wait.
He's busy.
Next round.
Irish Wolf Terrier.
No, Irish Wolfhound.
I guess so.
And this is,
I don't know.
I can see the Kinkies.
And this is Udu.
Hi, I'm Udu.
Cutie.
She's not here.
Do you want a biscuit?
We're at Niti Bagh.
Dog Saloon.
It's a bit spicy here.
Pet Saloon, that is Niti Bagh,
has dogs here.
Before and after,
you can view. You can check out.
You can bring your dogs here.
You can groom your dogs here.
You can groom them
and clean them up.
You can make them
out.
And see this cutie.
I met Karan sir.
Exactly.
Let's go there. So many people are there.
See people, you can bring your dogs here.
Even if they don't bring them,
you can still come here and buy things for them.
You can learn about dogs.
You can talk about them with different people.
With known people.
And now, let's see.
We're going to that place.
There you'll find awesome breeds,
awesome collection of people
from different backgrounds,
from different niches.
We should go to that.
Which breed is that?
That is a San Bernard.
Hey Azhar.
Good morning. Is this your dog?
It's a nice dog. What's his name?
Ustad.
His dog's name is Ustad.
Actually we're people from Duwang.
And we're a promotion club.
So,
The break is over.
What's his name?
Tiger.
Look at guys.
Awesome.
He got scared.
It's a Cocker Spaniel.
And we guess so another round of
competition is gonna happen here.
And no, it won't be a race
because dogs are of different breeds.
So, it won't be a fair competition
for them.
But let's see what happens now.
So, this is a race.
And here is Bikini Malia.
Let's see.
Dimension is the winner.
He's running so fast.
That Labrador is running after the girl.
He's running after her.
Yeah!
She left everyone.
Correct.
That is Julie.
And she's very fast.
And yeah.
So, people.
Hope you enjoyed. You had fun.
We're at the GST club.
Talk show organized by
Kennel Club of India.
You can check the show schedule
at KCI website.
And hope you had fun.
We had lots of fun.
We saw awesome dogs.
Awesome breeds.
And hopefully
we hope
you have a good place for dogs.
So, love people.
Obviously love people and also love animals.
Let the peace fall upon earth.
Adios.
Thanks for watching.