As Extension educators, we get frequent phone calls concerning paper wasps and their nests.
And as a home gardener, you'll probably run into these things at one point in time.
Now, this is a little bit of a problem because paper wasps are actually a beneficial insect.
They're out collecting caterpillars off of your crops.
But the problem is, when you get too close to them, they're indiscriminate stingers.
Your spring cleaning and getting ready for gardening, it's a good opportunity to take
those and just remove them from where they're at.
And usually they're found in the eaves of homes and structures, and they can be knocked
down with a shovel or other implement, and then taken away and thrown away.
So if the wasps have built a nest in a location that could potentially be a threat to yourself
or your family or your pets, it's a good idea to go ahead and remove it whenever you possibly
can.
And that can be done chemically.
There are products available that are specific to wasp and hornet control.
And wait until evening, spray that product so that all the wasps are on the nest.
And then once they've all died, you can clean that wasp nest off just like you would this
one that's in the eave that we have already removed.
This is Jeff Edwards, University of Wyoming Extension, From the Ground Up.