What's the number one question people ask about fixed gear bikes?
How do you stop?
How to stop on a fixed gear bike is the most frequently asked question from moms, pedestrians,
or other people who can't believe you're riding a bike with no brakes.
There are lots of techniques to stop a fixed gear bike.
The one we recommend is by using your front brake.
But if you're going to be a real G and you got rid of the front brake, here's some tips
that will help you slow your roll.
First, the skip stop.
This is a technique where you skip on your rear wheel, gradually slowing you down.
When you land, the bike skips and reduces speed.
Put a few of these together and you just save yourself from crashing into that parked car.
Hey, what's up guys?
I'm New York and if you're wondering how to do a skip stop, I got your answer.
First of all, you want to get up to speed.
You then want to rise out of your saddle, which will take weight off the back wheel.
Then using your feet, you're literally going to pick up the back wheel, which will basically
stop it in midair.
Also, keep in mind, whichever foot is forward is the action which you pull up with and whichever
foot is back is the one you push down with.
Basically, those are all the steps to do a skip stop.
A skid stop is where you lock up your rear wheel, causing your bike to skid and slow
down.
This is a fast way to stop, but it also eats up your rear tire.
In order to skid, you need to be going somewhat fast.
Rise out of your saddle to take weight off the back wheel.
Pull up with your left pedal by pushing down with the right pedal, keeping in mind that
your pedal should be horizontal.
If you need extra leverage, you can always push your leg against the top tube of the
frame.
And that's pretty much how you do a skid.
The easiest way to slow down is to apply back pressure to your pedals.
It really looks like nothing, but pull back on the pedals as they rotate and you'll slowly
cruise to a stop.
When riding fixed gear, it is very important to have some kind of foot retention on your
pedals.
You can either use straps or clips.
Either way, you need some kind of foot retention to perform any of the stops we've shown today.
If you have any questions or comments, we want to hear from you.
So hit us up on our Twitter at PureFixTV or drop us a comment right down below.
Tune in next week for a new episode on PureFixTV.com.
Until next time, I'll see you in the streets.