Hey, Rex here with 2 Wheel Oklahoma here in Dallas.
I ran into Felipe Smage.
The Spanish trials rider.
That's right.
You may have seen these guys on America's Got Talent.
How long have you guys been riding?
We've been riding since we were around 10 or 11, so about 13 or 14 years.
Wow, okay.
We've been going to town for quite a while now, but to ride trials it takes that long
to even ride the bike.
Exactly.
It takes a long time, but once you get to that level it's one of the most fun sports
you can do.
It is a lot of fun.
It's great exercise too.
I understand you guys compete, right?
Yeah, actually I try to compete.
My brother, he competes very well.
He's the four time national champion.
I hold my own.
I ride pro class very long with him, but usually he's at the front of the pack.
I'm just trying to beat a couple guys.
Right.
I'm just trying to get in there, though, both competing.
What's been the reaction?
I bet all the guys, like Sherco and Gas Gas, the guys that make trials bikes probably just
think you're the greatest thing to come along.
Have you increased awareness of the sport?
That was actually not only increased awareness of the sport, because that was one thing that
we really shoot for.
We love the sport.
We love to spread it.
That's kind of why we travel around doing demos, to bring the sport to new people.
There's no better medium than national live television.
Not only were we able to bring and grow what we're doing in our shows and our name, but
also the sport of trials, and then even motorcycling as a whole, because it's got a very negative
aspect by a lot of the world.
They think of motorcycles, they think of pollution, they think of death, they think of injury.
What we did, we were able to bring it into a tight, confined area, indoor, in a building,
in downtown LA.
By jumping these barriers, we were able to open some eyes and make people realize that
maybe the motorcycles aren't such a bad thing.
That was a really big thing that we brought from the show.
It was a really cool experience, and to be able to open up people's eyes in that aspect
was really awesome.
And you scored a gig at the International Motorcycle Show.
And we're here after it, so it was all good for sure.
So you're going to go around all 12 of them, right?
Yep, yep.
That's great.
We got one down two weeks ago in San Mateo.
We're here in Dallas, Texas.
It was a while getting here.
We had some transmission issues, tire blowouts.
Oh, really?
I mean, still haven't slept since we left to leave here two days ago.
We're running on thin right now.
It seems like you're really a rock star.
Yeah.
So this is what that feels like.
Oh, cool.
In that case, wow.
Well, there's some other things that go along with that, too.
Yeah, so it's been really good.
We're going to do the whole series, and we've really been able to get our name out there,
and we're booking more shows.
And we're doing what we really want to do, which is entertain people on our bikes.
That's what we've been working for years to be able to do, and now that we have that ability
and the option to do it, we're pushing for more.
Doing what you love for a living.
What a great idea.
Well, we're going to go have a seat and watch the show, and I wish you luck, man.
Hey, thanks a lot.
Enjoy the show.
We need somebody to jump over.
This guy in?
Thanks a lot, man.
Nice to meet you.
Thanks.
Thank you for watching.
Come on over to the tent, get some autographs from these guys.
We've got some free posters for you.
You can get some of these awesome GOAT shirts we've got.
Give these guys a high five.
Give them a handshake.
They're tired.
Give them some treats and give them some support too.
Isn't that great.