Hello, Gong Hei Fat Choy, and I don't know how to say it in Mandarin, but Sir Paul will
come and say it in Mandarin too.
What's going on?
We are at Main Street, no not Main Street, we're at Chinatown in Vancouver, British Columbia,
and we're coming here for the Chinese...
It's Chinatown.
Chinatown, and we're here for the Chinese New Year parade.
What's the date today?
February 10th.
And it's going to be awesome.
It's Sunday.
There's lots of hot jandis going all around.
I'm loving it.
Oh yeah, baby.
And Sir Paul, I don't know where he went, but...
He went to the pastry shop.
He went to the...
He's going to the pastry shop.
Woo!
Whoa!
Ah!
I just realized it's you!
Close your eyes.
So in Disney, the dreams that you first want come true.
Thank you.
Security!
There you go.
Smile!
That's a little smile.
Thank you.
She enjoyed that.
The Disney Strip!
Rooks, Gong Hei Fat Choy.
Rooks, sorry pal, Gong Hei Fat Choy.
I think there's dragons going that way.
Oh, look at that.
Oh, slow down there.
Ouch!
Yeah!
Hello.
Hi.
You're fired.
Thanks.
Thank you.
Happy birthday.
Thanks.
Thank you.
Happy birthday.
That's where I was sitting.
I was sitting right above a needle.
Thank you.
We are at the Dr. What's his name?
Sun Yat-sen.
Chinese garden.
And we just saw the parade.
It was fucking wicked.
Lots of hot jaundice.
I'm chilling here with Sir Paul.
Professor Bestestie is holding the camera.
Yo, yo, I'm on the camera.
And yeah, basically we're having a good time.
Big lake here.
Lots of fine honeys.
And great architecture from one of the best countries in the world.
One of the oldest civilizations.
China.
And we're just going to have a look around and see all the cool shite that they have up in this small pub.