🎶
🎶 Well I Heard That Rachie is Back! Igheheirenseieritz, recolored by viewer's caidenclawser 🎶
You gotta set to the goals
If you're searching for a way out
You gotta take a new road
If you don't keep the motion moving
You cannot feel the same
In the heart of the city
Where the streets are the veins
Oh, when I'm riding low
Oh, when the river's dry
Oh, can you help me go on
One more time
We're gonna get up for this
We're not gonna stop
We're never gonna run and hide
If I get down and say that I wanna change my mind
Put me in a circle
So I can change it one more time
Circle, circle, circle
One more time
We're gonna get up for this
We're never gonna run and hide
If I get down and say that I wanna change my mind
Put me in a circle
So I can change it one more time
Circle, circle, circle
I don't know where I'm going
But I know where I've been
And it's never in the knowing
It's in the not giving in
And when the earth is slipping, tripping