There's nothing more frustrating than getting a puncture. In this short film I'm going to
explain how to repair a tyre using the compressor and sealant kit that's provided in ŠKODA
vehicles. Having the kit in your vehicle increases space and reduces weight. It works by distributing
a sealant around the inside of the tyre which seals punctures, allowing the tyre to be re-inflated.
We're away from the main road here and away from the main risk, so now we can start the
repair. First of all, apply the parking brake to prevent the vehicle moving accidentally.
Next, ensure the gear lever is in the neutral position for both manual and automatic transmission
types. And finally, make sure all passengers leave the vehicle and move to a safe area.
The kit works on punctures no more than 4mm in diameter. The kit cannot be used if the
wheel rim is damaged or the vehicle has been driven with an under-inflated or flat tyre
for an extended period. If you can't use the puncture repair kit, you will need to
arrange vehicle recovery by contacting ŠKODA roadside assistance. The kit comprises of
a compressor unit and a sealant kit, which also has a valve tool, spare tyre valve and
warning sticker in the bag. Now take the warning sticker and place it into the driver's field
of view. Then take the sealant bottle and give it a good shake. Make sure it's all mixed
up and then attach the filler tube to it like this and make sure it pierces the foil. Now
we remove the valve cap from the tyre valve itself. And using the removal tool, pop it
into the valve, unscrew and remove the valve completely. Don't worry about losing the valve
as you have a spare one in the kit. Now we get the fluid and attach the filler tube to
the tyre valve. Hold the sealant bottle upside down and fill the complete contents into the
tyre. It doesn't matter where the tyre valve is located when the vehicle is stationary
as the sealant will work its way around the tyre when the vehicle is driven. Disconnect
the filler tube from the tyre valve and refit the valve insert back into the valve using
the removal tool until it's tight. Now we take the compressor, which is this item here,
and open up the front cover which gives you access to the electrics which plug into the
12 volt socket inside your car and also the inflation tube that will attach to the actual
tyre itself. Now we attach the tube to the tyre valve like this. Connect this section
to your 12 volt socket and then start your engine. Turn the compressor on by the switch
here. The tyre will start to inflate. Keep an eye on the gauge for pressures. These can
be found on the inside of your owner's manual or on the inside of your fuel filler flap.
It will take a few minutes to inflate. If the pressure stays below the required level,
drive the car a few metres to spread the sealant around the tyre. If it consistently stays
low then the tyre is too badly damaged and you will need to arrange a recovery. Once
inflated to the right pressure you can disconnect the tube, pop your tyre valve cover back on
and drive straight off. There are a couple of important points that you should be aware
of when first driving off. The tyre sealant will move around inside the tyre so it is
absolutely vital that you stop after 10 minutes and check the tyre pressure using the gauge.
If the tyre drops below the pressures outlined in the owner handbook then it could be that
the tyre is too badly damaged. If it's ok then you can drive on. But first remember
these points. The sealant means that you can drive at a maximum speed of 50 miles per hour.
Accelerate, brake and corner gently. It's a temporary measure so please see your local
Skoda retailer or tyre retailer immediately who can repair or replace the damaged tyre.
So I hope that's shown you just how easy it is to use the tyre repair kit. But please
remember this film is to be used as a guide and you must read the instruction manual thoroughly
before using the kit. And of course if you have any further questions please do not hesitate
to contact your local Skoda retailer. Thanks for watching this short film.