Hello, I'm Chef Dianne DeMayo and welcome to my kitchen.
Today we are making something super delicious as always.
We are making a Reuben sandwich with what?
Homemade corned beef, sauerkraut, and you can see the recipe on one of my bootleg tip videos.
We have some homemade pickles, again another wonderful bootleg tip video you can catch.
Swiss cheese, rye bread, we're making a very quick, easy Russian dressing.
And you wonder why I have a side of mustard here?
Because I have to take little tiny bites of the corned beef in between talking.
Okay, so let's build this sandwich.
First I'm going to get out rye bread.
Now you can use any type of bread you want.
You don't have to use rye bread.
You don't have to use dark rye bread.
I'm going to say this really quick because I can do it that way.
Get it on your plate.
Next we're going to start building.
I like fat so the fat stays on.
Layer one, layer two, there we go.
Bam.
Next I'm going to put another layer here of some queso cheese, Swiss.
Smash it.
On top of that, some bootleg sauerkraut.
And a quick and easy do-it-yourself Russian dressing.
But we're going to do the Russian dressing on the side.
Why?
Because I said so.
And I like to dip it in.
And sometimes I like to alternate with mustard because I am like that.
So all that really is is just some ketchup and mayonnaise.
You can do it the other way.
And then I'm going to put a little bit of the Russian dressing on the side.
But all that really is is just some ketchup and mayonnaise.
You can add some oregano, some garlic, some salt, some onions, some capers.
Whatever you want.
I like to keep it simple.
Ketchup and mayonnaise.
I kind of like 1,000 eyelid dressing and I'm going to leave that there.
And here's the key to making this something super yum yum.
I'm going to slather one side with butter.
I'm gonna slather one side with butter.
And then we're gonna take it to the stove,
gonna get it hot on one side, flip that bad boy over,
put a little butter on the other side, and booyah.
It's gonna be a hot, crispy, buttery,
delicious Reuben sandwich.
Let's go to the stove.
Okay, my pan is nice and hot.
I got my buttery side.
I'm gonna do a quick and easy turn.
And while that's doing that,
I'm gonna sneak up on its back end
and get some butter all over that.
Give it some pressing.
All right, let's flip him over.
Oh yeah, look at that.
Reuben sandwich out of the pan, onto my plate.
Nice, crispy, buttery crust.
Got my knife.
We're gonna cut this in half.
Now it's time to taste.
But I almost forgot, gotta have a little pickle.
Just a little bit.
Oh, how much I love you.
You are my friend.
Okay, so a little bit of this, and there's a system to this.
One bite, ready?
Booyah, that was a touchdown.
Corned beef sandwich, homemade,
bootleg style sauerkraut, bootleg style pickle
with a little bit of Russian dressing,
Swiss cheese, rye bread, butter.
Best sandwich ever, and I will see you next week
with another delicious dish.
Hello, I am Chef Diane DeMayo, and welcome to my kitchen.
Today, we are making a corned beef.