So this is a table, it's nice isn't it? Table and chairs. Very nice you might say
you know but there's a story behind it come with me. This table just got
delivered but and this is where the story begins. A truck had to obviously
deliver something as large as that and the truck got stuck there in the
distance is the truck. As you can see the truck ran off the road nearly tipped
over went down the gully. So here's the gully that could have gone down as you
can see we've tied it secured it with a piece of dental floss which will surely
hold should the truck trip over. There's also this tree which is sort of holding
it on. Let's look down the side shall we? There we go there's the truck. That's my
brother Paul laughing in the background. Here's the dental floss that's holding
the truck up sort of. Whales off the ground on one side and this is all
because my brother wanted a table. Put so many people out look at that almost
ready to fall down the ravine. So this is only half the drama because there's a
truck coming that's gonna try to pull us out. That'll be a lot of fun and we'll be
there ladies and gentlemen we'll be there. There's great forces are brought
to bear on this stuck truck that Mark made. There you go look milliseconds away
from doom. It stopped the driver who's a large husky Maori guy let out a girlish
squeal and as you can see the doors still open from where he leapt pirouetted
and landed on the ground. As the sun sets on another day in paradise we look at a
debacle that only Mark Young could be responsible for. Now we've got another
big truck to pull the truck that Mark got stuck in the rut because of a table.
Mark's stuck truck the bat truck
closer and closer they get
there's a lesson for us all
as you can see they're going to employ the pal finger an ominous sounding
named piece of machinery. This is the man responsible
without whom the situation would never have happened
Mark's stuck truck
as you can see Mark is basically marinating in stress over this
holds himself directly responsible for this calamity
so
there you go
and there's a solution here it is the deep ruts of despair caused by this
stuck truck of mine. As Mark leaves the scene of the crime the two trucks
rescue truck finger pal and Mark's stuck truck peel off and with a laugh falling
branch leave the property there you go what an adventure