Here at Pet Joy they have the state of the art equipment.
The cages for instance are stainless steel, they're veterinary cages.
They have wooden slats, many cages don't have these so if the dog has an accident he's not sitting in, you know, you can see it goes through.
And after grooming, we make little bedding for them to make sure they're comfortable.
And so they tend to lay down rather than sit up waiting.
Their tables, a lot of places have tables that don't lower.
So here, if you want to demonstrate Rosie, for instance if a dog is hurt or heavy it's not a good idea, it's not good for the groomer and it's not good for the dog to lift him up.
You can hurt the dog's hips, shoulders, and it's bad for the groomer.
However, so we have tables here, can you show how, so really fun, really good equipment, state of the art, they advise.
So the dog can come on, jump onto the table and then we can elevate the table.
Some bark a lot because of anxiety so we try to minimize any stress, any stress.
You know, if they're little, if they're nervous on the table we stop, we just take a moment to comfort the animal, calm him down.
So it works, you know, just a little time spent prior to grooming makes the groomer's job much easier.
So we know them well, we know their habits.
We try to sell really good quality food, grain free in particular, and there's, you know, we have some raw as well.
There's a big movement toward raw now.
It's what dogs have been eating for thousands of years.
So we have, we look for foods that are, you know, with like not factory farm salmon but rather wild caught, you know, salmon, things like that.
Grain free, gluten free, you know, those are serious issues for dogs.
I mean, a lot of commercial foods have fillers that they can't process, their bodies can't process and they become ill.
You know, dogs that should live until 19 are getting sick at 9 and 12.
So we like to carry really good quality food treats and we welcome feedback.
We welcome a lot of feedback.