It's the granddaddy of bike tricks. Either you can do it or you can't. Today
we're gonna teach you how to wheelie.
Hey guys, doing a wheelie is something we've all desired to do since our very
first bike ride. It's all about balance. Once you get it, you can ride the wheelie
for miles. My buddy Cole is gonna show us how it's done. Go ahead and do it man.
First, get comfortable pulling your front wheel up. Then push with your lead
foot and lean back. Practice this riding around an empty parking lot, but don't
use your straps just in case you have to bail. Now once you're able to get the
front wheel up, you need to find a balance point. So try maybe going to a
wall and holding on and finding that balance point until you get comfortable.
Let's put it all together. Ride forward and pull the front wheel up. Once you
push off your lead foot, lean back and find your balance point. Once you are
locked in, remember it's a combination of shifting your body weight and the speed
that you are pedaling. Thank You George. I'll have to practice that as soon as
I'm done here. As always, hit us up on our Twitter if you want to talk or drop a
comment below. Until next time, we'll see you in the streets.