Okay.
Is it on?
Yeah.
So what are we doing, Kate?
We are on our way to go watch the sun set.
We're gonna meet up with Rebecca.
Yeah.
So it's gonna be like a...
We're gonna get coffee by the end.
We're running late.
You know, this happens.
Hey Sean, what are you doing over there?
I'm trying to get us to see the sunset.
That is quite pathetic.
Are you taking the long route there?
I can't say that to him.
But that was my fault.
I got a phone call. I have a Cadillac CTS.
A really nice one.
My wife went out with two of her friends.
They get talking.
Yeah.
$2,000 worth of damage.
The two tires on the driver's side.
You hit a curb.
The rims of the tires.
That's the...
I know. What are the...
Yeah.
Well, luckily this one's not worth a lot.
What did you say?
I said, luckily your car's not worth a lot.
Let's go look at it.
No.
My other one I brought.
And he was like, oh gee, it needs a battery.
I'll send you the money. I'll buy a battery.
But, you know,
he didn't have to pay any bills on the damn thing
to get up there.
He just got a new battery.
He complained, oh gee, I can't get up there.
I bought it so he could ski.
I bought it six years old
and he can't go skiing.
The poor young guy.
Look really closely in between the trees.
You can see...
Oh.
I wonder if we can see Rebecca on her way.
How about your flat tire?
We could definitely see that.
Oh, maybe you should have driven.
I wonder what happened.
What do you think?
Now we're waiting for Rebecca to get here with her jack from her car.
So we can change, I can change my tire.
And we're going to have some Cadbury.
Oh, hey, look what I found.
Cadbury Easter eggs
with solid milk chocolate
with a crisp sugar shell.
Should we open them and try them?
Sounds...
I was going to say delicious.
Sounds delightful.
Let's open them and see what they taste like.
Did you like our old friend?
We're friends on Facebook.
Rebecca's calling me.
She probably got a flat tire.
Hello?
We're at the
San Remo condo.
Oh, there's Rebecca.
She's pulling over here.
She can't see.
Maybe I should buy that car.
Oh, no, there's rust.
You can see the rust under it.
Oh, here comes Rebecca.
This doesn't look good.
How's it going?
Come on, muscle man.
I don't know how to get in there.
We've been having fun taking videos.
The adventure of karma
and friends.
Maybe it's...
I think it's attached
in there with a
jack tool.
Do I need to move this chest
thing out?
No, your chest is fine.
It'll just be a
distraction, Rebecca.
Oh, my legs burn. My inner thighs.
Did you get it?
Yay!
Freaking duh!
Show us happiness.
Show us happy faces.
Yes, we are.
We got it.
Sean, have you ever done this before?
No.
Do you feel manly?
I'm kind of stupid.
Where'd he come from?
He's from the family.
I'm not sure.
I'm going to eat another piece of chocolate
while they're figuring out what to do.
See a little Cadbury egg.
I stepped in the ant pile.
That's what I get.
The instructions.
They're upside down.
Let's see.
They're over here.
Oh, for cranking?
Oh, we don't have a knob.
Yours is different.
How's it going?
Well, I figured out an alternative way
to spin things around.
Turn things around.
Oh.
So it's an adventure with you,
Shawny.
You can flip tires.
Wahoo!
Heck yeah!
Well done, my friend.
Oh, gosh.
How are we going to recover this bad boy?
Ouchies.
It's from too much dancing in the car.
Do you need Rebecca's help?
No, it's on me.
I feel so bad I can't help, Shawn.
It has to be lined up right.
You're going to get a hernia.
Let Rebecca help you.
Good job!
Oh, jeez.
What I don't like about tires
is that you have to not tighten them
all at once.
At the same time, you have to go one at a time.
Thanks for saving us.
And then I'll tighten it really tight
when I'm on the car.
Rebecca's to the rescue.
I know, aren't you proud?
Ladies, take note.
Shawn can chain a tire.
Go, Shawn.
I see a little bald spot
in the back of your head.
It's a scar.
I was in a bad jump rope accident.
Now, the key to being successful
in life is to always have a spare.
A backup plane, if you will.
So, that's a spider.
Now it's dead.
Did I get them?
Kate's just calling her dad to see if I did it right.
Why is it your life? It's my car.
My battery's gone. Oh my gosh, it's going to die again.
In the air?
Because they need to be tightened more.
Like a lot.
Well, can you ask dad?
Who are you talking to?
We did it!
Who's me? You did it!
Is there anything you would like to say?
I'd like to thank the Academy.
I'd like to thank
being voted Best Director for this short film.
It's a huge inspiration for me.
I didn't think I would get that.
I didn't think I'd be nominated.
Sean, I'm so proud of you.
And, the sun is down.
Victory dance!
The funny thing is,
he's actually a good dancer.
This is Sean trying to win my heart.
I love you.
Jerry, look at Jerry.
He's so concentrated on finding the tip.
Seriously?
Seriously.
Cole's embarrassed.
Rebecca's already done.
I can do it now.
And Sean's still working it out.
I love you.
I love you so much.