I get very, very irritated with food that when you bite into it, it burns your mouth.
And then you have this thing you want to eat and you've got to blow on it for a few seconds.
And fried chicken can be deceiving because on the outside, you might just tap it with
your finger and be like, all right, that's ready.
But it's trapping heat that could burn your tongue.
So I think it's important with a fried chicken sandwich, you lock the temperature, texture,
ratio dialed in, where when you hand it to somebody at a festival, they can eat it without
fear of burning their tongue.
So I'm all about getting that texture on the outside, the moisture on the inside, and the
heat balance dialed in.
So I think when you get all those elements together, those are the main key factors I
look for in a fried chicken sandwich.
Hi, my name is James McDuffie.
I'm the chef here at Joseph Leonard in the West Village.
What makes our fried chicken sandwich different?
It's a great question.
I think fried chicken is one of those things, like a burger, that it's in its simplicity.
You can do it really, really well.
Or you can do it haphazardly and it comes out not as amazing.
And I think ours is one of the better ones in the city, although there are some other
fried chickens out there that I aspire to.
The chicken is brined, then marinated in Tabasco and buttermilk, then dredged in seasoned flour.
And it's crisp.
It's awesome.
I would go toe to toe with anybody out there on a fried chicken competition.
I want something that's going to bring some acid to my chicken sandwich.
I want something that's cold, like we use pickled cucumbers.
I want something that's going to be cold, it's going to bring nice acid, it's going
to balance the temperatures as well as the richness.
And really, I think the right use of acid helps food enhance and explode in your mouth.
I think the toppings make it unique.
I think just the way the chicken itself plays with the honey and the sweetness and that,
the spiciness and the Tabasco, the crunch of the cucumber and the radish in it.
I think it's a unique sandwich.
I think it's delicious.
It's one of those things, we've tried taking it off the menu.
And we've had a lot of pushback from guests who come on a regular basis for it.
And so we keep it around.
My philosophy on food, I think ultimately, no matter what, it boils down to one common
principle which is the intention is to create a product that we're proud of that makes the
person eating it smile.
This is a damn good sandwich.
So you know, we wanted to do what we call an American bistro here.
Because we're in America, I'm American, part of my family's American.
And then within that, offer a few inflictions of French food that we love.
We are trying really, really hard to make connections with our guests.
We are trying really, really hard to establish real, sincere, genuine, deep connections with
the people that walk in our door.
And then if you're doing it well, then maybe that's unique.