One of the things that most riders have difficulty learning and everybody wants to be able to do is to whip the bike
Basically whipping the bike is exactly kind of what it sounds like you off the face of the jump
Basically whip the bike out sideways so that the goal would be to get the bike either, you know parallel to the ground
Or beyond which some riders are able to do on
On sizable jumps, but really to start with it's just kind of kicking the bike out and it's a natural progression
Some people get confused as to what actually goes on in the whip and how you get the bike back
But when you do the whip correctly the bike and the momentum of your bike will actually bring you back around and straighten you out
Before you hit the ground
The key thing is to not obviously go above your ability level or try to go
You know too far down or just also making sure that you're on the right type of jump to be able to whip it on
The key is
In the approach to the jump
We're actually almost leaning into it
Using the sidewalls of your tires to kind of bite as you take off the face of the jump
which will bring the bike actually flat as you leave the as your tires leave the
take off of the jump and
What momentum will do with it at that point is just kind of carry it back around and then over so there's a point
Where if you actually still framed it where you would be?
flat kind of this way and then as it comes around you're going to be out more to where your your
Tires are or sideways from where you were taking off and that whole thing will carry through
And it'll set you your bike back up straight as long as you do it, right?
The key is just very very small steps
learning to do it kind of
on real small jumps with maybe even a hip landing to where the takeoff would be
Straight to you, but the landing or the downside where you're shooting for would be at a an angle
Across to where you could actually land on a on a slope
You know over to your left if you can whip to your left or over to your right if you're trying to do it
To your right that gives you a little bit more room for a margin of error
To where you don't have to bring your bike all the way back perfectly straight, and you could land on the side slope
and it takes a little bit of the
Little bit of the risk out of it
So we're going to do a couple and kind of show you a little bit more of the technique in practice
So
As you can see
the whip is basically just a combination of
Taking off with the correct amount of lean and then using your body positioning to help bring the bike around
Depending on how much you know how far how little you got the bike out
The key is just to stay within your ability level
Start small and work up and up and up and make sure that
the jump has
When you're leaning against the jump your front end especially and your rear tire is not going to break loose on the face
Which would cause you to get kind of spiraling
Too far or it would make it very difficult to bring it back so stay within your ability level
Use your your body and your bike and let the momentum carry it across and you'll be whipping in no time
The whip is by far the most impressive looking trick and if you can master it you will be the envy of all your buddies
The important thing as I said earlier is just to take it slow
Analyze, you know the face of the jump find the right jump that you feel comfortable on
Begin the lean, you know, let the bike follow through in the momentum and your body position correct your
Correct your trajectory to get you back to straight as you get this feeling and you do it repetitively
You'll be able to go a little bit farther a little bit farther and and it can stay completely in control
Like I said, the whip is a lot of fun. It's it's fun to do. It's fun to watch and
Everybody should go try one