Hello!
Okay, tell us what happened.
Okay, well, um, second time driving and we were just like driving down the patch.
She was following the dog.
Yeah, and um, there was a snow drift and this car kind of got stuck in the snow.
So what were you two young lovers doing in the back 40 acres anyways all alone?
They were scootin'!
Driving, oh, okay.
I think they were scootin'!
He was hoping he was going to run out of gas.
Yeah.
He said he got stuck, so he said he got stuck, it was just as much fun.
You put too much.
You idiot!
We're a long way back.
Long, long, long, long way back.
What's the happy camper?
What was always happy?
I don't know.
We just had to walk all the way back?
Well, yeah, there you go, you're in a big drift.
Yeah.
Oh, that's old snow, I don't know if we're going to get out.
That's old snow from before the melt came.
That's hard snow, we're probably stuck for good.
Oh boy.
Oh, we'll see what he does.
Yeah, you're, um, I think you're stuck for good.
This we don't even know, do we?
Well, that's, yeah, it's pretty bad.
We're eating thorn bushes.
Yep, there's no use digging this one out.
No, so what are we going to do?
We'll have to leave it and hope the Indians don't destroy it.
Push, push everybody.
No, we can't get it out.
Then push the other way.
Push the frame.
Push the other way.
We need 50 more kids like you and we might have hope, but the way things are looking,
just take the key out and we'll have to take the Subaru back.
You got the key?
No, it wasn't that simple.
All right.
Why don't we try?
It was a hell of an adventure, wasn't it?
Oh, fuck, the check, the check.
Don't even know what to say.
She never forgot her first day driving, so never forget her second day driving.
Right?
Yeah.
Right, Wolf?
Wolf will show us the way.
He found a mouse on me and walked back.
Did he eat it?
Almost did.
Got in his mouth and I think it bit him or something.
Yeah, a little bite.
No, there are things that go along the edge of the front window, but they made it look more racy.
Okay, all aboard.
Hey, can we go home and do the cornfield?
Yeah.
Hey, I made the front.
Let's go.
Not anymore.
I think it's funny how Wolf is...
Can I sit there?
Michael, we're driving back through the cornfield.
I'm not sure.
Hey, everybody.
Good, I get to back with my brothers.
Oh, cool.
All right.
Here comes the cornfield.
Here, you can film.
Catherine.
Yeah.
Is there snow coming in back there?
That's fun.
See, when you get to be a good driver, you can do this all you want, then you come out.
Hey, J.K., did the hills give you butterflies?
The hills don't give me butterflies out here.
J.K., seriously, did the hills give you butterflies?
No, they give me bumblebees.
Who wants to go on Sky Hill?
Yeah.