Hello I am Chef Diane DeMaio and welcome to my kitchen. Today I am making a
chicken torta and I'm using a special bootleg tip breadcrumb with cotija
cheese and cilantro so make sure to check out that video. But today we are
making a very authentic torta using black beans, any kind of black beans that
we're gonna fry up, fresh avocado, we have some chipotle peppers, some jalapeno
oopsie, jalapeno peppers, queso blanco, you can use Oaxacan cheese or any type of
panela cheese that you want and if you can't find that use mozzarella. We have
thinly sliced chicken breast and a couple of eggs. Alright let's get cooking.
I'm gonna do a little prep and then we're gonna get the food over to the
stove. First thing first gonna get my tomatoes cut. I like to use Roma tomatoes
just because I like Roma tomatoes but you can use beefsteak tomatoes, you can
use any type of tomatoes. A tomato is a tomato, not necessarily, but I like my
Roma tomatoes. Alright just enough for the sandwich on the plate. Cheese, I love
this cheese. It's salty, it tastes good, it's kind of like a mozzarella if you will.
That's good. This melts very well. Some cheese from Mexico they don't melt.
You'll find one that you like and use it. Alright, an avocado. I don't like my
avocado too mushy, I like it just right.
Bam. Get this on the plate like that. Next, yes you got it, we are going to bread our
chicken. Okay this is an easy process. First what I do is I get my eggs in a
bowl, whisk it a little bit and then we're gonna dip our chicken into the
eggs and then into the breading and that's it. Then we're gonna go to the
fryer. Easy whisk. And there we go. And the huevos. Into the crumbs. Make sure it's nice and
crummy. And onto the plate. We're gonna do just one more piece because we want a
very fat juicy sandwich. Alright, there we go.
And there you go. I got my two pieces and I am ready to go to the stove. First
thing I like to do, as always, get extra fat into my meals. How am I gonna do that?
I'm going to butter my bread and make it nice and super crispy. Oil the pan, flame
is nice, and in goes my bread. Meanwhile, I have my fryer oil ready to go and I'm
gonna get my chicken inside.
While that's going on here, I'm gonna get my bread out of the pan, get some beans
into the pan, and just do a nice little heat smash. So I have some, how you say,
lightly fried beans. I think about one more minute for my chicken and it's
ready to come out. You can do this same recipe with steak, like a milanesa. You
could do it with fish if you wanted to, or you can do it with actually pork and
make the same torta sandwich. That's right, you can. Alright, my beans are about
done. I gave it a little more smashy smash. Okay, chicken's coming out.
Oh yeah baby, look at that. Cilantro still nice and green. Yeah. Okay, and it goes,
and I'm gonna do it while I'm here. Yeah, that's right. I'm just gonna sear some of
this bean on now. Okay, we are now going to do something that takes a lot of
concentration, extremely serious. We're going to build a torta. We have our black
beans already at the bottom layer. That's right. I'm gonna add some cheese. Then I'm
gonna do some tomatoes. I'm concentrating very hard, you have to. There you go.
Tomatoes. Shall we? Okay, we shall. Now we're going to add chipotle sauce on one
side like this. Yes, there it is. Then we're going to smother that with some mayonnaise
because I can.
Lettuce, and I'm gonna give it a nice little crunch so it kind of breaks it up.
You could cut it up into little slicks, little tiny tiny tiny tiny tiny tiny
slivers, but why? Why? What's the point? And then to make this sandwich, ultimately
the chicken torta, we are going to add pickled jalapenos. That's right.
We're just gonna lay it across. Okay, I got my lettuce on, I got my jalapeno
peppers, and that's right. Fresh avocado going on there and there. I'm gonna have to break it up and
smoosh it in. And the question here is how I'm gonna wrap my mouth around this.
All right, that's it. Crowding this bad boy. Sandwiches of sandwiches. The chicken
torta, breaded in breadcrumbs, cotija cheese with a little bit of cilantro,
black beans, queso blanco. Bam! And now I'm ready to eat this.
Mm-hmm. Mm-hmm. Okay, that is too good. Mexican street food ain't got nothing on
me. Don't forget to check out my bootleg tip for my breadcrumb and cotija cheese
mixture, and I will see you next week with another super tasty dish. Ciao.
Hello, I am Chef Diane DeMaio and welcome to bootleg tips. Today we are making
something very easy, very useful. What is that? Breadcrumbs. Flavored breadcrumbs.