How did you get started in this?
My daddy was a beekeeper and I kind of followed along with him.
And after I got through teaching, why I added a few more hives.
They are undertaker bees, guard bees, nursery bees.
They go through all those different stages in the hive.
Cans of syrup that we feed the new hives when we start them.
And there's one that goes on each hive and the bees are able to get the syrup out of
these cans when they're sitting upside down by the cloth here.
We can go over here and open up a hive and look and see what the bees are doing.
Now you going to get in trouble with those bees by opening up that hive?
No.
See they're working on a honey super now.
They're building new comb here, new comb here on the, this is what we start with and they
can see where they're building the new comb.
How come they don't get mad at you?
Because I'm handling carefully and I'm gentle and they like my smell.
They know who you are.
Yes.
There's a drone bee.
Which one is he?
This big guy right there?
Yeah.
How do you know he's a drone bee?
Because of the size of him.
He's got a rounded butt.
And they're filling the honey super from the maples and the early blooming flowers here
in Washington.
There'd be about 60 pounds of honey in that top super and one frame will produce three
or four pounds of honey.
Wow.
And how long does it take them to do that?
That depends on the honey flow and how many bees you got in the hive, how much honey you're
going to get.
So if you got a full two boxes of honey, bees in the bottom, why you can in a good honey
flow fill one of these honey supers a week.
How many bees would you say are in a hive?
Is there any way of knowing that?
Approximately 60,000 in August.
They build up during the summer and you end up with 60 to 70,000 in August and early September.
Do they stay in the same hive?
Is it like a...
Yeah.
They all got oriented to this one place.
That's their home base?
Home base.
And they are into the sun and the magnetism of the earth.
If this was cold weather, you wouldn't do this.
And why not?
There'd be too many bees in the hive.
This is a three pound jar of raw Washington honey that my bees make.
We sometimes have fireweed honey or blueberry honey or the blackberry.
You look, you see some pollen in it.
That's why they tell people to buy honey from a local beekeeper if you have allergies.
This is where we get queens out of Hawaii, in a little package like this.
Really?
Yeah.
Now what does a queen cost you?
They're in the neighborhood of $20 this year.
They're going sky high.
I just shipped six of these jars to Anaheim, California.
People from down there like the local honey.
You get it down there.
I mail it to them.
They mail me the check and the freight.
Oh, these are doing real well.
They're clean across the top of the box.