Hold fast.
Instructing.
handle another go around, so we're going to let Gary go this week.
I'll keep it short and sweet.
I want to talk to you just real quick about what we tell our players, and I think it will
help everybody here on the show.
Now obviously, we all go through adversity.
We go through adverse situations.
Be it something major that happens to your family or to you or something minor, find
out a friend's lying to you or something like that.
We all deal with it differently.
But we say to some of our players, and it's called, we ask them consistently to play the
next play.
Don't get caught up in the play that just happened.
Play the next play.
And if you think about the quiet edge of your life, don't get caught up in the things that
are behind you or the things that are going to just go play the next play.
And I think it will really help you with the things that you are attempting to do, be it
sports, school, whatever it is.
I've got a quick little analogy for you.
The players have heard this.
I'm going to bust it out.
There's a little folklore, and this is relatively true because I just made that up.
But I'm going to bust it out.
There's a tribe that survives on catching monkeys out in the forest.
These monkeys love coconuts.
They love the insides of coconuts.
Stay with me here now.
What these tribes would do is tie a rope to a coconut, and they would cut a hole just
big enough at the end of that coconut so that the monkey could take their hand, stick it
inside the coconut, and then grab the sweet insides.
The problem is this, though.
When the monkey would go to pull their hand out, it couldn't get it out.
So the tribes would come along, pull the rope in along with the monkey, and now they're
done.
Here's the moral of the story, and I want you to remember this.
All that monkey had to do was what?
Let go.
All it had to do was let go.
So tonight at the game, when you're watching, when our players are playing, let's not get
caught up in the great things or the little things or the bad things that happen along
the way.
Let's keep marching forward.
Keep playing.
Keep hammering.
Keep getting after it.
And you do that tonight, you do that at school next week, you do that for the rest of your
life, and good things will come your way.
I guarantee it.
Thank you.