Hey everybody, what's going on? It's Josh Beach here and this is the first episode of War Man's Meals.
So let's go ahead and get right into it.
I was thinking to myself the other day,
Self?
Huh? Huh? Huh? What? What do you want? Huh?
Yeah, that's not my name.
Okay.
Um, what is your name then?
Ha ha. No. Turd Ferguson.
Okay, Turd Ferguson.
Yeah, what do you want?
What should we do? I've got some hot links, I've got some ketchup, I've got some onions. What do you think?
Peppers. Peppers. Gotta have some peppers. Put some peppers. Peppers.
Obviously myself is being stubborn, or Turd Ferguson.
So, bottom line is this. We're going to be making some spicy sausage sandwiches.
Mmm, yeah. I can't wait.
Green pepper.
Onion.
Simple.
Cheap.
Sixty cents. Sixty cents. Cheap.
But what do you need in order to cut those onions and peppers?
Sharp stuff.
Hey man. Hey.
Knife sharpening.
Hey, hey, now leave me alone. I'm playing Rad Racer.
Mmm.
Cut it.
And cut it good.
Peel that onion.
Mmm. Cutting onions. Being a man.
Mmm.
Mmm. Ow. I got goose in my eye.
Hey, what in the world man? What's going on?
Geez, next thing you know you're going to be burning your face off. Give me a break.
Don't eat a whole onion.
Flake it off. Onions are layers.
Layers of onion.
Be good.
On a spicy sausage sandwich.
Cut them thinner.
Don't want it too thick either.
Nice and thin. Slices.
Not like the big stupid bite that I took.
Small.
Green pepper. Green pepper. Take the label off.
Labels are nasty. Not good for one's health.
I don't know what the white stuff is, but you don't want it.
Pepper strips.
Helps stop you from crying from the onion.
Fresh pepper.
And it wouldn't be spicy sausage sandwiches without...
Boom. Spicy hot sauce.
The best. How much were these back? One buck. A buck.
Alright. We've spent, how much now? 220?
Not including tax?
What's the last ingredient?
All natural. Ketchup in a bottle.
Yeah, that's right. Look at me cover the label with my hand.
Why? Because they're not a sponsor. That's why.
How much was the bottle? Two bucks.
The whole meal costs less than five bucks. Now that's a poor man's meal. Let's cook it.
If you can't stand the heat, get out of the kitchen.
We're going to cook this for about 45 minutes.
What's that going to do to ketchup? Caramelize it.
Oh yeah, ketchup.
How much ketchup? Enough.
There you go.
Always remember to shake well.
Add links. Right in.
That's what I'm talking about.
Peppers and onions, right on top. Boom.
Don't want the ketchup to get in the way.
Finally, cover.
And what's wrong with my cover? It's too big for my pan.
Why? I don't know.
I don't have pan covers. I'm just poor. Sorry.
Leave it sit for about 45 minutes. Let's see what happens.
Blink of an eye. Blink your eye. Maybe snack time.
I'm going to eat this.
Blink of an eye. Blink your eye.
Maybe snap a finger. 45 minutes will go by just like this.
The beauty of it is, it cooks for 45 minutes right here on the stove.
This kind of thing you can stick in a crock pot and cook for 7 hours.
I wouldn't recommend cooking it any longer, but still.
Cook it for as long as you need or think necessary.
It's good. Low heat. Don't want to over boil it.
You can see that ketchup caramelizing already.
It turns into like a natural barbecue sauce with those green peppers and onions.
Good stuff.
Now, bread. Not just any bread.
But you're going to want to get yourself a stadium style bun or a hoagie.
Why? You need something with a little bit of size to it.
A little hot dog bun is not going to work.
Now,
get yourself a lake.
Just like that.
Mmm.
Get yourself a spoon of the sauce and veggies.
Mix it up a little bit here.
There we go.
That's what I'm talking about.
Get some on there.
Some more onions. I'm an onion lover myself.
Green pepper.
And bam.
Just like that.
Spicy sausage sandwiches.
Yum. And freaking hot.
Let it cool down a little bit.
Mmm.
Now that is a tasty poor man's meal.
One of my favorite things to do.
Thanks, Dad.
So, I hope you enjoyed it.
Join me next time for another episode of Poor Man's Meals.
And until then, keep on eating.