We have a party right here.
Yeah, it's much more comfortable around them.
Oh, thank you.
This will be a cool detail.
What do you do when I'm with them? I'm like on the kids parade.
Do you want to get in front of me?
I'm alright.
What's up?
Are you serious?
Better ride faster than that.
My foot would have been in there soon enough.
It's all quiet. Real quiet for the cops.
Oh yeah, why get arrested before the parade?
Woohoo, say hi.
Thank you very much.
Yeah, we're the canine dog.
Canine units.
There they are.
Woohoo!
Yeah!
Go Kings go!
fairer forever equals justice.
Go Kings Go!
Thank you!
Wooo!
Thank you Bailey!
Go Kings Go!
Thank you Marty!
Wooo!
Thank you boys!
Thank you!
Thank you for bringing the comeback!
Wooo!
Yeah!
Thank you guys!
Thank you!
Wooo!
Go Kings Go!
Alright!
Wooo!
Thank you!
That was awesome.
I don't even care.
I was taking pictures I couldn't see.
I know.
I stopped aiming.
I just held it and started clicking.
Wooo!
So...
Click, click, click, click.
That was so close.
And all of them.
Look at all the people.
Almost all of them.
Yeah, a lot of them.
Wooo!
That was fun.
Cool.